♪No one can stop us, we rise through the storm♪
♪لا أحد يستطيع إيقافنا، نحن ننهض من خلال العاصفة♪
♪Even bleeding and broken, we'll still push on♪
♪حتى مع النزيف والكسر، سنستمر في المضي قدمًا♪
♪The earth quakes with furious might♪
♪تهتز الأرض بقوة شديدة♪
♪I'll hold your hand and charge into the light♪
♪سأمسك بيدك وأتجه نحو النور♪
♪Adventurers, a new tale begins♪
♪المغامرون، تبدأ قصة جديدة♪
♪Brave hearts in the real world win♪
♪القلوب الشجاعة تفوز في العالم الحقيقي♪
♪Sparks fly when courage collides♪
♪تتطاير الشرر عندما تلتقي الشجاعة♪
♪Burning bright, our crystal tears ignite♪
♪تحترق بشدة، وتشتعل دموعنا البلورية♪
♪Above this city we stand tall♪
♪ فوق هذه المدينة نقف شامخين ♪
♪Flying wild, we're breaking every wall♪
♪نطير في البرية، ونكسر كل الجدران♪
♪Love's grand adventure, we'll conquer it all♪
♪مغامرة الحب الكبرى، سوف نتغلب عليها جميعًا♪
=Keeping Up with Beauty= (Adapted from "The Highborn Matron Reborn as the Pitiful Heiress")
=مواكبة الجمال= (مقتبس من "السيدة النبيلة التي ولدت من جديد وريثة بائسة")
=Episode 23=
=الحلقة 23=
Shiqi's biological father has told us everything.
لقد أخبرنا والد شيقي البيولوجي بكل شيء.
The poison that harmed Grandma and you,
السم الذي أضر بك وبجدتك،
and the drug slipped into my wine,
وتسلل المخدر إلى نبيذي،
all came from him. He gave them to Shiqi.
كلها جاءت منه. أعطاها لشيقي.
And besides that,
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك،
he even handed over some recorded calls.
بل إنه سلم بعض المكالمات المسجلة.
Shiqi was...
كان شيكي...
We have proof and witnesses.
لدينا الأدلة والشهود.
Everyone has to pay for what they've done.
يجب على الجميع أن يدفع ثمن ما فعلوه.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Mr. Gu,
السيد جو،
the eye specialist we contacted from the U.S.
أخصائي العيون الذي اتصلنا به من الولايات المتحدة
arrived in China.
وصلت إلى الصين.
You can have your surgery soon.
يمكنك إجراء الجراحة قريبًا.
Maybe,
ربما،
you'll be fully recovered in no time.
سوف تتعافى بشكل كامل في أي وقت من الأوقات.
Gu Chenyu's eyes will be healed soon.
سيتم شفاء عيون Gu Chenyu قريبًا.
Yunyun,
يونيون،
it's time for you to do what you must
لقد حان الوقت لتفعل ما يجب عليك فعله
and go where you're meant to be.
وتذهب إلى حيث من المفترض أن تكون.
I...
أنا...
Even if you want to stay,
حتى لو كنت تريد البقاء،
Fu Zhengkang's death
وفاة فو تشنغكانغ
will always be between you two.
سوف يكون دائما بينكما.
Don't you still feel guilty
هل لا تزال تشعر بالذنب؟
toward Fu Yunyun?
تجاه فو يون يون؟
I understand.
أفهم.
Once his surgery's done,
بمجرد الانتهاء من الجراحة،
I'll leave.
سأرحل.
I'll get going.
سأذهب.
Okay.
تمام.
Be safe on your way.
كن آمنا في طريقك.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Is this Ms. Fu Yunyun?
هل هذه السيدة فو يون يون؟
Yes, speaking.
نعم، التحدث.
We're from the Haicheng City Public Security Bureau, Jiangzhou.
نحن من مكتب الأمن العام لمدينة هايتشنغ، جيانجتشو.
My name's Li.
اسمي لي.
We have updates
لدينا تحديثات
about your father's death to confirm with you.
بخصوص وفاة والدك للتأكيد معك.
(We found a surveillance video)
(وجدنا فيديو مراقبة)
on Gu Shiqi's computer.
على كمبيوتر Gu Shiqi.
It's connected to your father's death a year ago.
إنه مرتبط بوفاة والدك منذ عام.
We've already arrested Gu Qingshan.
لقد ألقينا القبض بالفعل على Gu Qingshan.
He's confessed to everything he did.
لقد اعترف بكل ما فعله.
An officer will be in touch with you soon.
سوف يتواصل معك أحد الضباط قريبًا.
Please cooperate.
من فضلك تعاون .
Fu Zhengkang.
فو تشنغكانغ.
What are you doing here again?
ماذا تفعل هنا مرة أخرى؟
How many times do I have to say it?
كم مرة يجب أن أقولها؟
I will never sell the Jiangxing Hotel.
لن أبيع فندق جيانجشينغ أبدًا.
Not even if I die.
حتى لو مت.
Don't be so stubborn.
لا تكن عنيدًا جدًا.
Think about your daughter.
فكر في ابنتك.
If you die,
إذا مت،
all those debts will fall on Fu Yunyun's shoulders.
كل هذه الديون سوف تقع على عاتق فو يون يون.
Even if you leave her the Jiangxing Hotel,
حتى لو تركت لها فندق جيانجشينغ،
she won't be able to keep it.
لن تكون قادرة على الاحتفاظ به.
She'll be at everyone's mercy.
ستكون تحت رحمة الجميع.
By then,
بحلول ذلك الوقت،
Chenyu can buy Jiangxing at an even cheaper price.
يمكن لـ Chenyu شراء Jiangxing بسعر أرخص.
How dare you use Yunyun to threaten me?
كيف تجرؤ على استخدام يونيون لتهديدي؟
I'll give you one last chance.
سأعطيك فرصة أخيرة.
The Jiangxing Hotel,
فندق جيانجشينغ
are you selling it or not?
هل تبيعه أم لا؟
Never!
أبداً!
Gu Qingshan,
قو تشينغشان,
I'd rather die than sell it to you.
أفضّل أن أموت على أن أبيعه لك.
You brought this on yourself.
لقد جلبت هذا على نفسك.
Fu Yunyun,
فو يونيون،
your father's death
وفاة والدك
can finally be avenged.
يمكن الانتقام أخيرا.
(Gu Qingshan was convicted of murder,)
(تم إدانة جو تشينغشان بتهمة القتل)
(extortion, and embezzlement.)
(الابتزاز والاختلاس)
(He was sentenced to death for his crimes.)
(حكم عليه بالإعدام بسبب جرائمه).
(All his personal assets were confiscated.)
( تم مصادرة كافة ممتلكاته الشخصية .)
Have some water.
خذ بعض الماء.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
The surgery will go smoothly.
ستتم العملية الجراحية بسلاسة.
When my eyes are healed,
عندما تشفى عيني،
will you be leaving?
هل ستغادر؟
(Does he already know I'm not Fu Yunyun?)
(هل يعرف بالفعل أنني لست فو يون يون؟)
Back then, Third Uncle did what he did
في ذلك الوقت، فعل العم الثالث ما فعله
because of me.
بسببي.
I can't deny my part in it.
لا أستطيع أن أنكر دورتي فيه.
But Yunyun,
لكن يون يون
I want to try again.
أريد أن أحاول مرة أخرى.
Let's start over.
دعونا نبدأ من جديد.
Give me another chance.
أعطني فرصة أخرى.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
I...
أنا...
If you're willing,
إذا كنت على استعداد،
I hope that...
أتمنى ذلك...
when I open my eyes again
عندما أفتح عيني مرة أخرى
the first person I see...
أول شخص أراه...
is you.
هو انت.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll think about it.
سأفكر في الأمر.
Mr. Gu,
السيد جو،
we can head to the operating room now.
يمكننا التوجه إلى غرفة العمليات الآن.
Please come out safely.
يرجى الخروج بسلامة.
Ms. Fu.
السيدة فو.
There's something
هناك شيئا ما
I think you should know.
أعتقد أنه يجب عليك أن تعرف.
Mr. Gu spent a lot of time and effort
لقد بذل السيد جو الكثير من الوقت والجهد
collecting your paintings
جمع لوحاتك
from different stages of your life.
من مراحل مختلفة من حياتك.
He even organized this exhibition just for you.
لقد قام بتنظيم هذا المعرض خصيصًا لك.
Actually, that day...
في الواقع، ذلك اليوم...
was supposed to be a surprise for you.
كان من المفترض أن تكون مفاجأة بالنسبة لك.
The brushwork is quite delicate.
إن عمل الفرشاة حساس للغاية.
Yeah, it's beautiful.
نعم، إنه جميل.
Very imaginative.
خيالي للغاية.
(Fu Yunyun's Personal Oil Painting Exhibition)
(معرض اللوحات الزيتية الشخصية للفنان فو يون يون )
(There's one more thing.)
(هناك شيء آخر.)
(Mr. Gu asked me to pass this on.)
(طلب مني السيد جو أن أنقل هذا.)
Actually, he...
في الواقع، هو...
He had already guessed who you really are.
لقد خمن بالفعل من أنت حقًا.
But he said,
ولكنه قال
no matter who you are,
بغض النظر عمن أنت،
it doesn't matter to him.
لا يهمه ذلك.
(He just wants to spend the rest of his life with you.)
(إنه يريد فقط قضاء بقية حياته معك.)
(Mr. Gu hopes)
(السيد جو يأمل)
(you can start over in this world,)
(يمكنك البدء من جديد في هذا العالم)
(with a new life,)
(مع حياة جديدة)
(a new beginning,)
(بداية جديدة)
(free from all burdens and restraints.)
(خالية من جميع الأعباء والقيود.)
(From now on,)
(من الآن فصاعدا)
(live freely, follow your heart.)
(عيش بحرية، واتبع قلبك.)
What a special exhibition.
ما هذا المعرض المميز!
Though I can't quite tell what the theme is.
على الرغم من أنني لا أستطيع أن أقول تماما ما هو الموضوع.
I asked the person in charge.
سألت الشخص المسؤول.
He said
قال
this exhibition is a gift.
هذا المعرض هو هدية.
The name is
الاسم هو
"True Love".
"الحب الحقيقي".
♪Words I can't say linger on my tongue♪
♪الكلمات التي لا أستطيع قولها تبقى على لساني♪
♪Each time you're near, my heartbeat runs♪
♪في كل مرة تكون بالقرب، ينبض قلبي♪
♪Cold nights glow with gentle stars above♪
♪الليالي الباردة تتوهج بالنجوم اللطيفة في الأعلى♪
♪My silent thoughts stretch long like dreams of love♪
♪أفكاري الصامتة تمتد طويلاً مثل أحلام الحب♪
♪How do I hide these feelings so faint and shy♪
♪كيف أخفي هذه المشاعر بهذا القدر من الخجل والضعف♪
♪When I meet you again, warmth flows quietly by♪
♪عندما ألتقي بك مرة أخرى، يتدفق الدفء بهدوء♪
♪My eyes can't help but turn your way♪
♪لا يمكن لعيني إلا أن تتجه نحوك♪
♪I close them tight, pretending all is the same♪
♪أغلقهم بإحكام، وأتظاهر بأن كل شيء متشابه♪
♪The wind brushes softly by♪
♪تمر الرياح برفق♪
♪Carrying half of my sigh♪
♪أحمل نصف تنهيدة♪
♪I walk a while, then glance behind♪
♪أمشي لفترة، ثم أنظر خلفي♪
♪You bring back warmth I thought I'd lost♪
♪لقد أعادت لي الدفء الذي اعتقدت أنني فقدته♪
♪My pain quietly thaws♪
♪يذوب ألمي بهدوء♪
♪And in silence, loneliness fades away♪
♪وفي الصمت يتلاشى الشعور بالوحدة♪
♪Because you are my light in the dark♪
♪لأنك نوري في الظلام♪
♪I'll be your sun when winter feels too hard♪
♪سأكون شمسك عندما يصبح الشتاء قاسيًا جدًا♪
♪We shine for each other through the quiet and the loneliness♪
♪نحن نتألق لبعضنا البعض من خلال الهدوء والوحدة♪
♪You are the warmest light in all my world♪
♪أنت أدفأ ضوء في عالمي كله♪